hey guys what's up welcome to another
video from bringing in this video I'm
going to tell you guys a little bit
about my University I'm going to try to
tell you how I went through the whole
process of like you know applying for
scholarships applying for the degree
getting to university starting
University and how my university is like
so what I'm sort of you and let's get
started I have been to Chinese
universities before so this was not the
first time I was applying for a Chinese
university so I had a little knowledge
about how to go through these processes
and what to expect when getting at
university basically I started out by
looking around for a degree I really
wanted to study I knew that I wanted to
study in English so and that kind of
limited the degrees very fast
basically I only found two degrees with
the journalism in English and those two
were two universities in Beijing one was
one I am doing right now and the other
one was another one at Shanghai
University which is a better University
than one I do right now
about because I chose this one because
of other reasons as well after finding
the University I wanted to go to I
applied for the scholarship I also
applied for the University it's two
separate application procedures so you
have to make sure that you apply for
both and then first I receive one and
then I received the other and I was like
yay now I can do this after receiving
the confirmation of the scholarship I
send that to the University and tell
them this is my scholarship and then
they put it together and it actually
everything went really smooth then I got
a health check at home in Denmark first
and then I got my visa and then I went
to China I want to turn a little early
so in the beginning I couldn't go to
university because they didn't open up
before in the end of August or like the
beginning of September this is very
common so if you want to go to China
before that you have to make sure that
you have another place to stay cuz the
dorm is not going to be open before a
few days before University start anyways
so I went to the university I went to
international office I was looking
around where
in the beginning I couldn't really find
anything but I asked you to bid around
and everyone was really nice there are
some other Chinese University students
sitting on campus and waiting for the
Chinese students to arrive so they were
really helpful and they tried the best
to tell us where to go first I went
through international office and the
dorm and they signed me up and they put
me in a dorm room with another girl who
was really nice and then I put all my
stuff there as well and I was like
playing around for a week I got to know
some of the other people on campus some
of the other international students we
had some parties together it was a lot
of fun and then one week later our
trusses started I just followed the
schedule I met my classmates we had a
lot of fun together it was actually a
really simple process the university is
very nice it's the smaller than the
biggest universities in Beijing which is
lovely I think for me because then you
can bike around it's very fast to get
around and easy to get out of campus and
in again and a lot of and everyone there
is super nice also at campus would you
have like library cafes restaurants in
every supermarket or hairdresser and we
have all the classrooms of course and
the dorm and stadium and a gym and a
pool we had everything there so
basically your life can be only at
campus you don't even have to leave the
campus which i think is pretty awesome
so yeah that's like a little bit about a
university I'm going to show you guys a
few clips from my University campus
because I personally think it's so
beautiful you're not going to need
anything we also have a subway by the
way so if you can get a sandwich when
you're getting excited of Chinese food I
get that a lot so that's really lovely
for me anyways one problem though is
that my degree is kind of messy
basically I was supposed to study
international journalism but because
they have to English 12 degrees they put
them together because they're not that
many students so I study international
journalism and that's what's going to
say on my certificate afterwards but
basically I only study courses
concerning new media because that's the
other degree and it seems like more
professors like to talk about that I
don't like that part because I don't
learn to write anything and I also don't
learn the rules about your
in China I would have loved to know more
about that
luckily I'm also very curious about your
media and maybe I should have chosen
that degree instead of I realize this
later on so for me it's not that bad but
I'm just saying that don't expect too
much when you get to China it's more of
a cultural experience and it looks good
on your CV and like obviously if you go
to the best universities they're going
to be hard on you you're going to learn
more I see that with some of my friends
who are at such universities like that
you have more things they have to hand
in and write instead of that but not
that much at my university but it's time
for me because then I have time to do my
own thing and that was one of the
reasons why I chose a small university
because I knew this already at my
university we also have a lot of student
organizations we have a bar so it's like
you're never alone please never be
worried about this because when you get
to China there would be other foreign
students around and I promise you you
have so much fun you might get this
feeling of like being homesick I get
that because I think everyone has that's
not once in a while but it will you know
go away at some point you can check out
a video I made about this so that is
basically a little introduction about my
degree I'm going to study until next
year but I only have courses until like
in two weeks and we're going to finish
and somebody just sort of picture of me
we're going to finish this course very
soon and then next semester are we going
to do an internship and then the last
half a year I have to write my thesis
and scraped then I can finish next year
with a mustace degree from China it's
great experience and I want to stay here
that was my story about my university
here they're both good good and bad but
you know I love it here I really really
love it I do honestly love it I know
that some people like China and
but I really honestly love it here and I
hope that you will like it too
remember if you have more questions if
you want more personal advice you can
always look at my website laying around
bloopers the Skype need project and then
you can call me and we can talk and I'll
help you as much as I can ok the people
who are getting very curious so I'm just
going to leave it at that thanks for
watching this video I hope you're having
a great evening for ever you want world
and I'll see you again very very soon
meaning is out SIA and again bye bye
[Music]