hello and welcome to another video Ling
Ling is back and today we're going to
talk about all the things I can do or we
can do in China but that we can't do at
home of course it's from a Danish
perspective so it might be different
from your experience in China and in
your country but I'm just talking about
my own personal experience and please
leave a comment below about your
experience in your own country and China
or if China is your country China and
another country whatever you feel like
join the discussion I love to hear from
you so anyway without further ado let's
get started
let's get into this video the first
thing I feel I can do here but not at
home is to randomly meet and bump into
people and just add them on WeChat yeah
without a valid reason I talked to add a
nice guy about this last week and I was
like yeah you know here you can just add
people like you don't have to have a
reason you just add them and be like oh
yeah let's share we chat information
contact information and I'm like that's
amazing cuz you bump into so many
different people everywhere and people
who know people who know people like I
feel like my network social network is
growing so much fast much faster than at
home because in Denmark you really have
a really you need a really good reason
to add somebody if you don't know them
or if somebody didn't introduce or if
nobody introduced you to each other so
it is really cool here in China because
then we do need help next time you know
who to talk to and again you can you
know find them on your WeChat and text
them and you don't need a reason you can
just say hello what's up how's it going
and that's okay too
so yeah that's definitely the thing I
love to do here in China which I just
cannot do at home a second thing I can
do here but not really at home is that
here I'm already different so I feel
like you know I just embrace this
you know I just embrace the fact that
I'm different and just do whatever I
feel like because I'm different no
matter what I do I can wear what I feel
like I can do what I feel of course I
don't act like a crazy insane person or
do really like dumb or illegal things
but you know in Denmark it's just people
kind of dress very much alike everyone
looks very similar and you don't really
go and do something that's you know that
nobody else does and like so when I come
here and a good example is actually my
phone cases because you guys know that I
love the cute phone cases and Danish
people don't really do much like phone
cases and if we do it's only like a very
simple read of not red or white like a
white phone case so I love hear that if
I find a phone case that's insane I just
put it on my phone because nobody really
cares cuz I'm already different and of
course the Chinese people many Chinese
people do it anyway but I feel like
foreigners like my foreign friends here
they tease me a lot about those phone
cases and I get that at home as well but
now I've just you know I've embraced it
so much and like bringing around these
phone cases so when I go back to Denmark
I use them anyway and it gives me some
attention and sometimes negative but you
know it's mostly just for the fun of it
and it's amazing and it's a I feel more
free yeah because I'm already different
here so I might as well just embrace it
and go for it okay I know that that
third one some of you guys gonna be
probably gonna be angry with me uh
because the third one the third thing I
feel like I can do here but not at home
is to write on the wrong side of the
road and yeah I know that it's illegal
and I know you shouldn't do it but
everyone does it and it's pretty often
very difficult to change to the right
side of the road because of big fences
or bridges and stuff like that so I give
you an example when I come when I bike
to my work I have to go on the wrong
side for a little bit until I meet the
first lights cross lights and anything
of traffic lights and then I could cross
I could if I wanted to drive the
opposite direction for half a mile and
then turn around in the lights there and
then go back but I'm a lazy and everyone
else does it and the same when it comes
to the traffic lights if there's green
light that way first I Drive that way
first if there's a green light that way
first I go that way first and then I go
deal I don't know if that makes any
sense but people they bike together with
pedestrians so it's very common that
you're biking on the wrong side but it's
convenient and because the Chinese
traffic lights it takes really really
long time to change from red to green so
that's what people do and I love that I
can do it here in Denmark even though
there are no cars at the traffic lights
I'm still stopping and waiting because I
know if the police comes around I have
to pay a big fine and I don't like that
of course and yeah it's just not really
cool you don't do that in Denmark but
here it's just you know whatever suis
bien bah okay the fourth thing really
amazing thing that you can do here in
China but not really at home is that
it's not that expensive here so you can
eat out every day without going broke in
like two or three days in Denmark that
would be impossible if you have to even
just if you buy like a sandwich if you
look at the same amount of money of
course if you're in Denmark and a
full-time worker of course you have more
money but I'm just saying let's say if I
had five thousand here and five thousand
in Denmark it would be much cheaper here
and because many people never cook here
so the food and restaurants also cheaper
because it's more common to go out and
eat for dinner and lunch instead of
going home and making your own food so
that's really great I can go out and be
social much more than I do at home I
tend to invite my friends to my house at
home to like keep the cost down but yeah
I really like to be outside and be
social so that's an amazing thing I can
do here in China but not really at home
then we have number five number five you
guys can
I'm so disgusting when I say this but in
China
something I can do here but not at home
is a burping and farting and spitting
yeah because it seems like burping is
whatever nothing nothing here in China
you burp and then you move on
farting the same thing I feel like when
people do it here they don't like nobody
really seems to care um and this meaning
again you just blame the pollution and
yeah the farting burping you just blame
the food so yeah ice is something you
can do here very free it's very free I
also see people picking their noses but
yeah I'm I'm not gonna do that but I'm
just saying you know if I accidentally
borrow if I fired outside I don't give a
shit
and then because nobody else gives you
so that's really convenient really nice
free freedom yeah anyway those were my
five things that I can do here in China
but not really at home so as again as I
said in the beginning please leave a
comment below with whatever you feel
like you can do in China but not at home
or what you can do in China but not
abroad or you know what I mean I hope
you like this little video from Ling
Ling and yeah until next time I hope
you're having great dear evening
wherever you are and I'll see you again
soon see ya
and sigh Jen and I bye
you