good morning guys good morning what's up
how are you welcome to no it's not a
blog
how are you what's up thinking is back
with another video and today we're gonna
talk about the top 5 apps you need for a
more convenient and better living in
China yay ok so let's just get started
the first app the first time is for
socializing and it's for you know just
being able to have a very convenient
life in China you probably guessed it if
you been here before if you know
anything about Chinese apps well we got
the WeChat or in Chinese cold ways in
which you recheck recheck weekend yeah
so first we chat is really important
because when you meet new people in
China especially young people we don't
swap like the business cards anymore
which is what we check information but
I'm telling you when you're swapping
these information please immediately
when you swap them write the name you so
you can remember who the person is
because Chinese young people have a
tendency to write Nick mix forever
waiting for the reach and nibs and it's
really confusing when you want to find
them again you can't find it because it
change the name and usually also don't
use their own profile picture like so
you see your contact information with
little dog as a profile picture and the
name is like dignity it you know how
would you know anyway so you can choose
their content name so they can't change
it
mm um so that's pretty cool WeChat is
also really convenient because you can
pay with the recheck wallet in many
different stores I'm going to make a
more specific video about that later on
because that's another thing
ah you can top up your phone with WeChat
I'm going to show you that later as well
top up your phone you can find a cap you
can send the print envelopes as persons
to your friends it's many differents and
more and more and more so many other
things that I even haven't discovered
yeah there are so many cosmetics good
feature
so wechat for socializing for
everything else get your reach head
downloaded right as I am speaking
another really important one number two
is also is called a li p as the a museum
you can find it it is in english so you
can interpret it if you don't speak
Chinese really convenient a leap a
Pawnee Hey in Chinese is culture for
bombs above and down below as well and
all my information right now I'll write
it down in the description box so take a
look there um so a leap a observable you
can use that to pay wherever you go you
can pay online you can pay for food you
can pay in shops many shops you just
scan the code and the QR code and it
amazing I'm telling you they may see so
yeah get your alley paint or jerubbaal
for finance stuff very important album -
okay then we have act number three this
one is food for fun activities for
cultural stuff for new your travel and
everything in between really it's very
difficult to you know explain because
there are so many possibilities within
one single app so the third app is
called reach one I know I probably say
wrong because I don't know I just grew
out the tone
it may 2008 down below so sorry for that
different serum but um this one is
basically you can go in there you can
check out food nearby you you can water
why my takeaway there were come to your
door with the food you can also see
which restaurants good where can I get
some discounts you can see where can I
find my my my massage if I want a
massage you can go and find the cause by
Friday which I want to go and find very
very soon at 7:00 see you back even
though I'm not sure if this app is in
English so I'm sorry for that in advance
but ask a Chinese friend to help you
little bit in the beginning or install
like hope on your phone and use that
it's really convenient um and really an
app you note if you sit down and look
around there lots of pictures so it kind
of makes sense really fast even though
your journeys so Chanyeol and get those
three apps okay we have number four
number four is for transport that's
those days when you just really hate the
subway and you don't want to take the
basket of smelly I tell them to get it I
have been there then this app is really
smart it is called dee dee dee dee da
dee dee natura so basically you can find
all the Texas nearby you and you just
right I'm here I want to go to there and
then you can like okay and I think that
part should be in English I'm not
promising but I think it's in English as
well which could be very nice right and
because it's a part of or it was in
reach enten to be checked before so
I'm not saying anything to say no I'm
not saying purchasing I'm not promising
anything but to say in English so you
can find Texas all around - or you can
also download mover if you had Cooper
and hope when you come to China
uber is working perfect to find as well
one problem is just that when you're
caught when you're finding your driver
try these drivers they do not look at
the map and drive there where you are
and find you they will call you so be
prepared many foreign is they don't want
to use uber on TV because of this
because they're nervous and they don't
in the Sun was it rock is going to say
um customer service is not really a big
thing in China so some of the drivers
can be quite angry but last time I
Trevor he called me and like what are
you and it was like I'm at my door and
he was like oh I can't get there you
have to go find me and I was like I
gotta go again and he was like I've
already been waiting ten minutes it was
like ah you know um yeah so I actually
just bailed on him economy because I
couldn't find him but anyway sorry yeah
um that's the thing it goes both ways
right if they're so rude
I'm rude for that so DV or uber uber of
courses in English so that's a very
smart and DDI was insurance um then that
was for transport transport then we have
number five number five my favorite
number five you already know it and
you've seen some of my videos number
five is of course
towel towel well and I checked I can't
find an English version of towel I did
try to check online as well but I can
find an English version um I know that
my friend who doesn't speak or read any
Chinese he just checked how about
written online and then you would use
Google Translate or you know trance
homepage so it's like not the best
transition but you still can get around
which is very smart but again it's also
a very good way to you know what you
want to do online shopping it's a good
way to practice your Chinese so what I
did there are long words I didn't know
beforehand but then if I need it to buy
something a try but a nice plate a
sweater I would just you know search a
word on black I'll put it in Taobao and
then I would like search around and then
I could see oh they call it this but you
also call it that and in a sense
searching new terms and stuff like them
so it's actually really great way to
learn something while you're still yeah
so Tahoe is just the biggest online
shopping platform ever I want to do is
serious on how to survive China and I'll
give you all the tips and facts and info
about how to make your chinese lives
even more amazing because i love it and
like these apps just really makes make
your life much more convenient here so
yeah definitely
urging you all to win I'll put all the
names in the description box below and
yeah I hope you guys enjoyed this video
until next time have a great day evening
wherever you are in the world and
leaving some